<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Songyu Ye (叶松瑜）</title>
    
    
    <description>This website is a virtual proof that I&apos;m awesome</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/me/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Reykjavik</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks Rented a car. Important to take comprehensive pictures of the rental in the parking lot before and after your reservation. Also everything is so expensive. Gas stations put a hold on your card for approximately 300 USD, but they do release it. Also the speeding tickets are brutal...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/reykjavik/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/reykjavik/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Stockholm</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks Indeed airport lounge access on arrival works. Swedish Food Dish Pronounce Description Köttbullar [ˈɕœtˌbɵlːar] Swedish meatballs, typically served with lingonberry sauce and mashed potatoes. Gravlax [ˈɡrɑːvˌlaks] Cured salmon, often served with mustard sauce and dill. Smörgåsbord [ˈsmœrɡɔsˌbuːrd] A buffet-style meal with a variety of hot and cold dishes....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/stockholm/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/stockholm/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paris</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks BVA has no airport lounge Paris is terrible in the winter The prices are outrageous Chipotle portions are smaller here Happenings Ended up staying in the Pakistani neighborhood. Ate some really good lamb biryani. The Louvre is really insane. Really enjoyed the Denon Wing which houses the Mona...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/paris/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/paris/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rome</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks Dish Pronunciation Description Carbonara car-boh-NAH-rah A pasta dish made with eggs, cheese, pancetta, and pepper. Cacio e Pepe CAH-cho eh PEH-peh A simple pasta dish with Pecorino Romano cheese and black pepper. Supplì soo-PLEE Fried rice balls typically filled with mozzarella cheese and tomato sauce. Saltimbocca sal-teem-BOH-kah Veal...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/rome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/rome/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Tirana</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks I generally ate in cafeterias by the university area. Cheap Albanian home cooking. Contact me if you want the exact location. Albanians want cash because they are dodging credit card transaction fees and taxes. Euros are commonly accepted. However there is a liquidity issue where some stores will...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/tirana/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/tirana/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Vienna</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks Dish Pronunciation Description Wiener Schnitzel vee-ner shnit-sel A breaded and fried veal cutlet, often served with a slice of lemon. Apfelstrudel ap-fel-stroo-del A traditional Viennese pastry filled with apples, sugar, cinnamon, raisins, and breadcrumbs. Sachertorte sah-ker-tor-te A dense chocolate cake with a layer of apricot jam and a...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/vienna/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/vienna/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Athens</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks | Dish | Pronunciation | Description | |—————-|—————|————————————————–| | Moussaka | moo-sah-kah | A layered dish with eggplant, minced meat, and béchamel sauce. | | Souvlaki | soo-vlah-kee | Skewered and grilled meat, often served with pita and vegetables. | | Tzatziki | tsah-tsee-kee | A yogurt-based dip...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/athens/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/athens/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Istanbul</title>
        <description>
          
          General Remarks If you are planning to visit multiple palaces in Istanbul, consider ordering an ISIC Card online for 20 USD. This card provides discounts and is valid for entry to at least two of the palaces. It is a cost-effective option and worth using whenever possible. It also proved...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/me/istanbul/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/me/istanbul/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
